// Maths Questions
const questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " 19 + ……. = 42",
    answer: "23",
    options: [
      "23",
      "61",
      "0",
      "42"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the symbol of pi?",
    answer: "π",
    options: [
      "€",
      "π",
      "Ω",
      "∞"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Arrange the numbers in ascending order: 36, 12, 29, 21, 7.?",
    answer: "7, 12, 21, 29, 36",
    options: [
      "36, 29, 21, 12, 7",
      "36, 29, 7, 21, 12",
      "7, 12, 21, 29, 36",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the greatest two digit number??",
    answer: "99",
    options: [
      "10",
      "90",
      "11",
      "99"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How much is 90 – 19?",
    answer: "71",
    options: [
      "71",
      "109",
      "89",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "20 is divisible by ……… ",
  answer: "1",
  options: [
    "1",
    "3",
    "7",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "Find the value of x; if x = (2 × 3) + 11.",
  answer: "17",
  options: [
    "55",
    "192",
    "17",
    "66"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "What is the smallest three digit number?",
  answer: "100",
  options: [
    "100",
    "999",
    "111",
    "101"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "How much is 190 – 87 + 16?",
  answer: "119",
  options: [
    "103",
    "261",
    "87",
    "119"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "What is 1000 × 1 equal to?",
  answer: "1000",
  options: [
    "1",
    "1000",
    "0",
    "None of these"
  ]
},

];
